The world.
What a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
seize it, raise your flag, and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless everlasting
world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Someday, somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere?.
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart. But I know.
A brand new world
that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
A great long blue sky.
Weighing in the troubled waves.
From all despair I can be saved.
For the horizon on the other side is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is what I am for.
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began.
Overseas of green and shores of sand.
Through the endless
everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Someday somewhere I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere.
Captain!
One tooth is the size of our
boat! That's it! We're dead!
There's no monster!
This is just one big stupid dream that
we're all having together for some reason!
A dream, right!
It was just a dream!
You know...
Our boys just got eaten.
So did that ship we
were trying to salvage.
How can you be so calm?
Yep, most definitely eaten.
I can see the air hoses
dangling from its jaws.
Stop.
I can't stop.
I see my hair and my friends.
What am I going to do?
This is all your fault!
You're the one who said it would be
safe at the bottom of the Grand Line.
I don't know what qualifies
as safe in your book,
but in mine, it's not man-eating turtles!
You're right.
Sorry!
It's as good as it's gonna get, I guess.
If we don't cut the air hoses that beast
will drag us down to
the bottom of the ocean?
I don't care what you do just do
something you're the tough and
smart lady give me a minute I'll see
I'll see what I can come up with.
Okay, boys!
Time to save our noble captain!
Our pride, honor, and lives are at stake!
Our captain is alive and we will find him!
Mark my words!
They're right.
It's these challenging times that
prove the streak by which we are made.
Usopp! Yeah?
Cut the air hoses and get us out of here!
This is what we're made of!
What is that?
It's like everything got dark.
There's no way.
Why is it so dark?
It's not that late.
It's time to leave, guys! Now!
Luffy, Zoro, Sanji.
This is a bad omen.
We all know the suddenly darkened sun is
the harbinger of the monsters to soon rise.
Guys, we've got to save the
boss and get out of here!
Reef!
Tell me what happened!
Are you dead?
Where are the others?
Zoro! Sanji! Set sail now.
We've got to get out of here.
Yeah, that guy's crazy.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Now let's get away from the
stinky turtle as fast as we can!
No, it wasn't a turtle, it was a monkey!
Yeah, bonafide sea monkey.
Can't say I'm too surprised that he and
Luffy got along as well as they did.
Well, they're both monkeys.
But when he caught a glimpse of all the
stuff that we had taken from his ship,
he totally flipped out
and went on a rampage.
I've never seen a primate
act like that before.
Yeah, that's Mashida, the
king of all salvagers.
But never mind him, how did the three
of you escape from the giant sea turtle?
Ugh, why do you keep
talking about a turtle?
Hmm, that's weird.
Now he's just floating there like a
statue with his mouth gaping open.
Oh, I get it, of course!
That's how you guys escaped!
We were in that thing's mouth!
Nothing gets past you guys, does it?
That's the turtle that ate
the ship you were inside!
Hey, when did night happen?
Attention all hands!
We're getting out of here now!
Ah!
Not so fast!
Hand over the treasure you stole!
Or I'll tear your ship apart
and find all of it anyway!
Is he right?
You guys found some treasure?
We sure did! Tons of it!
This isn't good.
If he starts rampaging
the ship we all go down.
Hey, Captain!
Behind you!
What's behind me?
I don't know.
Sea Monsters!
That couldn't have been real.
Those things were taller than the sky.
The Grand Line is an endless
parade of mysteries and annoyance.
I mean, look at the nightmare
of just making it through today!
First there was that huge galleon that
fell from the clouds on top of us.
The Log Pose's needle
started pointing to the sky.
A psycho makeup wearing monkey
shows up and blocks our way.
And then a gigantic sea turtle
came and ate our salvage ship.
Then darkness fell.
Because the biggest monsters I've ever
seen in my life blocked out the sun!
I must admit, even I was
intimidated by those things.
Those monsters were too big
for any of us to take them.
Yeah.
If I never see them again,
it would be a blessing.
Don't sweat it.
They're nothing.
If I really cut loose, I could have
taught those sea monsters a thing or two.
Sure.
I fought ten of those things a while back.
You fought ten of them?
Come on, you guys.
Tell me you at least tried to find something
down there that we could actually use.
All you brought back was
a bunch of scattered junk.
There's not a single clue here
about how to get to Sky Island.
There wasn't anything there, believe me.
We looked. Yep.
If there was something else down
there, we would have found it.
The ship was in terrible shape,
all jacked up like it had
maybe been attacked and raided.
Or perhaps a mutiny had
broken out and they all killed
each other in a violent
struggle for power and survival.
Look around boys this is exactly why we
need more information intelligence means the
difference between life and death for this
whole crew and if we're
gonna sail to Sky Island
then we need more information to stay alive
or whatever happened to that ship could
happen to us too we didn't
brave giant monsters
so you could bring back a creepy octopus
some rusty swords, and a broken dish!
This is all junk, and you're all idiots!
What is that, Luffy?
Armor.
Whoa, she crushed the armor!
Nami, you didn't even notice the
pretty seashells I brought you.
Cram your seashells in your shorts.
She's so beautiful when she's angry.
You should still try
to keep your distance.
Bad day huh?
It's only gonna get worse
working with these guys.
We'll never figure out how
that ship sailed to the sky.
I'm gonna snap on them any second.
Maybe this will help.
Eternal pose!
But how?
Oh, I took it off that
salvager's ship earlier.
Just in case.
You're the only one I can depend on.
All right, who's up for
an octopus dinner tonight?
That boy has got to learn to relax.
Jaya, this must have been their home port?
Jaya, is that where we're going next?
That would be your decision, Captain!
All hands on deck!
Set our course to Jaya!
So, uh, any of you know which
direction that might be? Starbird.
You heard her, chopper. Right.
Onward to Jaya!
Now, hold up just a minute.
If we head off to this Jaya
place that's so important,
won't the Log Pose's needle
change its position again?
Because if that happens, we won't
know which direction Sky Island is.
What?
All hands full, stop!
Want to tell me why you're
messing with my head, Nami?
I'm not.
You're the genius who
decided we should go to Jaya.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Well, I didn't know it was going to
ruin our plans to get to Skypiea.
It's not my fault you have
the memory of a goldfish.
Think, the log poses always
work that way, hasn't it?
Yeah, guess so. Hey! Listen up!
I have an important announcement to make.
Seeing as I'm the captain, I say
we set our course for Skypiea!
How do you propose we get there?
We're gonna have to ask
for some directions.
Maybe someone in Jaya will know the way.
Very well, Jaya it is. Right!
On to Jaya!
You already said that!
I doubt that the needle would
change as soon as we get there.
So why don't we pull into port and then
leave before it has a chance to adjust?
Sounds good to me.
If we're lucky, it'll work.
That sounds like a plan to us!
Full sail to Jaya, people,
and this time it's for real!
Now stop stuffing your
faces and get to work!
I wonder what this Jaya place is like.
I hope it's relaxing.
Nami, my sweet!
Robin, my dear!
Dinner is served!
Looks like that's the last of your cash.
But if you wanted to, I'd let you
raise with, say, your clothes?
You're lucky and you don't even know it!
Playing with Roscio, even if
you would have won the hand.
Trust me, you would have
lost something else!
I suppose that about wraps it up.
You cheated this entire hand, didn't you?
I never cheat, you're a liar. You lie.
I watched every deceitful move you made.
You better watch your mouth
in this place, loser Sargus.
Hey Sargus?
Hmm, what is it?
This guy was cheating just now.
You saw the whole thing didn't you you
bet I did every rotten little move!
He cheated straight through
I said we do something
about this guy make an example out of him.
You have no idea who you're dealing with.
You see anything, Usopp?
Nothing.
Just the sky and the sea.
I thought the Jaya Island wasn't
too far from where we were.
It shouldn't be.
And with the weather being so clear,
we should have spotted the
coastline over an hour ago.
I'm going to like Jai if
it's as warm as it is now.
I'm finally getting to work on my team.
Spring weather's the best.
It looks like the Scales
are enjoying it, too.
Hmm.
They've been shot!
Looks like we'll be eating good tonight!
I don't think they could
have been shot, Chopper.
I didn't hear any gunfire.
I found a bullet!
And judging from the trajectory,
it came from that way!
Are you saying the shots came from
an island we can't even see yet?
That's impossible, Chopper!
But I saw it happen with my own eyes!
A tuna had a better
chance at killing them.
No sniper or gun has that kind of range.
They were probably shot before
and just happen to fall now.
Hey, Sanji!
Look, we found our dinner!
Poor creature.
He must have suffered.
I wasn't able to get an
instant kill on one of them.
But that's what fate held for him.
All the events of his life
destined him to this outcome.
So I can't.
Myself.
Hey jerk.
Do you know who I am?
No.
Get lost.
I'll tell you.
I'm the greatest.
Fighting champion ever.
Is
it just me or does this
place look like a resort?
It sure does!
Hurry up and dock!
It does look promising.
Maybe we can even stay here a while.
Hmm?
Either I'm starting to hallucinate or the
harbor over there is full of pirate ships.
Don't be silly, Usopp,
since when can pirates dock their ships
in a harbor without being run out of town?
You're right.
It must be a joke.
Someone help!
He's gonna kill me!
What the heck's going
on with this crazy town?
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
What a pathetic little weakling!
Ha, ha, ha!
Oh, Missy, you picked
the wrong guy to beat up.
Look at that emblem.
He's in Rocio's gang.
You have heard of Race, right?
You know the executioner whose
bounty is 42 million berries?
The man is psychotic.
You better watch your back.
That guy is full of it.
We watched that entire game ourselves.
No one cheated.
I still can't believe he was
able to beat up Race so easily.
Don't you know that's Bellamy? What?
That's Bellamy?
The one with the 55
million bounty on his head?
Captain!
I can't believe it!
Who did this to him?
We need to get him to a doctor!
Hurry!
Hang in there, Captain.
We'll get you mixed up.
Now this looks like my kind of town.
We'll have no problem fitting in here.
There's no way.
Do you think those two can last an
hour without getting into any trouble?
Well, by the looks of this place, I'd
say 15 minutes is a generous assumption.
You really think so?
I'd better say... Nami!
Luffy! Saru! Wait for me! I'm coming too!
There she goes.
Don't worry.
I'm sure she'll be fine with
those two protecting her.
I'm the only one who can protect Nami.
Master D!
Nami will be safe and
sound with Luffy and Zoro.
But if you leave, then what are we
supposed to do if this ship is attacked?
Don't leave!
Who's gonna protect us?
Fine, I'll stay behind.
Let me go.
I guess I'll whip up some tea
and hold down the fort, then.
Where did Robin go?
Huh?
I don't know.
Sanji, about that tea...
Make it yourself.
I got my tough face on, so
if anybody messes with me...
No fighting!
Promise me!
Yeah, yeah, whatever, I promise.
Good, this is serious business, you two.
Good.
Great.
Gee, thanks for the support.
Look, if one of you causes trouble here,
we'll have to get out of this town.
And if that happens, then we'll never
know how to get to the Sky Island, right?
Yeah.
Whoa, he's messed up.
Looks like he fell off his horse.
That's gotta hurt.
Looks like he's in pain, too.
No doubt.
Hey, sorry to bother you,
but will you help me up?
What, are you not in the
mood to help yourself?
Luffy, give me a hand. Sure.
Up you go.
Hey, would you look at that?
I'm on my horse again.
I was a sickly child growing
up and never got better.
Now let's get out of here stronger.
A horse, too?
We should put them out of their misery.
Thanks again, pal.
You know, I don't have enough money for a
reward these days, but care for an apple?
Do you take us for idiots?
We'd never trust food
from someone like you.
Hey, look! Apples! Luffy!
What the? What happened?
Some guys took a few apples
from that freak on the horse,
and when they bit it
to them, they exploded!
Oh, no! No!
Luffy spit it out!
Spit out the apple you just ate!
I already swallowed it!
What the hell did you do that for?
No worries, the boy isn't hurt.
What happened?
I don't know, but the inside's destroyed!
If you had eaten the bad one, you
would have died on the first bite.
You're lucky.
What is all this?
It's Oshio's grave now.
It looks like a war broke out here.
Did they fire a cannon into the
middle of town or something?
Who knows?
Even the people who were
there and saw what happened
said they couldn't tell
exactly what was going on.
About the only thing
everyone knows for certain
is that Bellamy had
something to do with this.
Bellamy the hyena?
I think it's pretty obvious that he's
using the power of one of the devil fruits.
What's the deal with this town?
I don't know.
Who really cares?
You should care, seeing as you
were almost killed for no reason.
Well, that was bound to
happen sooner or later.
Have you lost your mind?
Ah, great.
Look who's back.
How many victims has he racked up now?
It's not like he's a famous
fugitive or anything.
Who do you think he is?
I don't care, and to be
honest, I don't want to know.
If that meathead wants to be the fighting
champion, then go ahead and let him.
Fighting champion?
Hey, don't even think about it, you two!
Damn it.
I'm starting to wonder if we can
find any useful information here.
How about this place?
Seems pretty quiet to me.
You can say that again.
This place is gorgeous.
To think such an oasis exists in
the middle of this disgusting town?
It's built above the water.
That's great, but there's no one here!
Although I can smell
that someone's cooking.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, I'm going to have to
ask you all to leave, please!
See, the entire hotel has
been rented out by Mr.
Bellamy and his guests And
he's asked that we tell
other guests like yourselves
to go somewhere else?
So uh you must understand that
I have no say in the matter!
So one man rented out
this entire place? If Mr.
Bellamy sees you here, he'll have
my head removed from my body,
so please leave for my sake.
Come on, I'm sure he won't mind.
Who is this Bellamy, anyway?
What's going on here?
Who are these scumbags, and what
are they doing in our hotel?
Mr.
Sargus, welcome back.
I told them to leave,
but they won't listen.
I really don't care.
Just get rid of them.
We're paying a lot of money to
have this place to ourselves.
She's right.
Now get out of here
before I throw you out.
Hey, guys, would you
mind if I beat him up?
Please don't.
Luffy!
Ha!
You're going to beat me up?
Ha ha ha! Hilarious!
Here, go buy some new rags so
you don't look like an orphan.
Sargus, you're wasting your money by
tossing it to this bunch of losers.
Ha!
No kidding!
I should have just flushed
it down along with my lunch.
I'll take free money!
Let's go!
These jerks can't help us!
I can walk on my own, you know!
Sargus, Lily, just
leave well enough alone.
Eddie, we've been looking for you.
You know that trash you ran into?
Seems they've been doing
pretty well for themselves.
Look.
Not bad, but nothing
compared to you and Bellamy.
Here.
But for ordinary scum,
they can hold their own.
They still don't stand a chance of
surviving the transition into the new era.
Wow.
His bounty is 30 million.
For such a little puke.
I'm sure Bellamy will want to see this.
Man, that really pisses me off.
That's a shame, because, you know,
Mocktown's economy depends
on pirates throwing money
around to show off power
they may or may not have.
What, so poor pirates aren't
allowed on the island?
Looks like there's no
way of calming you down.
Here, this one's on the house.
Tough guys and degenerates are a clientele
here, so trouble isn't hard to find.
You weren't going to make it in
this town if you let it bother you.
You have to play it safe
when you can. Here you go.
This whole town's a real dump, you know.
Of course, that's how most
level-headed people would think of it.
But unfortunately for you, level-headed
people are rare in these parts.
The wanted posters won't be on
the walls for a couple of days,
so you may want to skip town
sooner rather than later.
A couple days?
That doesn't give us much time.
Now here's a question.
Hey, Bacchi!
Huh?
What's wrong?
This guy's Bacchi's fucking delicious!
This is one of the worst
drinks I've ever tasted.
I think there may be something
wrong with your taste buds, kid.
I think there's something
wrong with your big fat head.
Well, I'm not the cook in this joint,
so I don't care what you have to say.
Got it?
Hey, Barkeep, I'll take 50 steaks to go.
And I'll take 51 of those
delicious cherry pies to go.
Wait, make that 52 steaks.
Better make that 53 pie.
Fifty-four steaks!
Fifty-five pies!
Sixty steaks!
Seventy pies! Eighty! A hundred!
I'm gonna beat the living crap out of you!
Did you even have the slightest
idea what you're fighting about?
Luffy, you promised, remember?
Besides, we don't have enough
money to buy dozens of steaks.
We aren't here to shop!
Heh, so then, are you a pirate?
Yeah, that's right.
How big's your bounty?
Thirty million.
Uh, thirty million?
For you?
I wouldn't believe it
even if I collected it.
Are you calling me a
liar, you fat, hairy ape?
Enough!
We've got rules in this place,
and one of them's no fighting.
Here's your 50 cherry pies.
Now please, just walk away.
I'm looking for a pirate
that wears a Straw Hat.
It's Bellamy.
So you must be Straw Hat
Luffy worth a cool 30 million.
Who's this guy?
Looks like he has a bone
to pick with you, Luffy.
That must be that Bellamy guy that
rented out the hotel we were at.
Did you hear that?
The kid's worth 30 million.
No way.
Tell me about it.
How come everyone I meet
in this town is so tall?
I'll take a glass from the top shelf
and give the kid whatever he wants.
Right.
Look at this place.
This joint is packed solid.
This place is disgusting.
It smells like vomit.
All you can get here is cheap rum.
Look, Zoro.
It's those guys from earlier.
You'd be in a lot less pain if
you just offered us your seats.
Pathetic harbor trash.
It's him, Big Knife Sargus.
How much you want to bet
he's looking for a fight?
Oh, great.
The whole gang is here.
There's no way that they stopped
in just for a bite to eat.
Drop it, man.
It has nothing to do with us.
What's Bellamy up to?
The usual fun.
Cheers.
Hey, thanks for the drink, pal.
Well, you know what?
You're all right!
You did it!
Brilliant move, Bellamy!
Just brilliant!
What are you doing, punk?
That's the question you
should be asking yourself.
Zoro! Don't do it!
We still need to get some
information from - Quiet!
This guy wants a fight,
I'll give it to him!
So that's all you've got for backup?
Now, are you ready to take me on or not?
No way!
The kid just challenged Bellamy!
You'll be slaughtered!
You've got it all wrong, kid.
This isn't a fight.
It's a test. Now, come on.
Let's see how strong you are.
Luffy, hold on.
Mister, we're trying to
get to the Sky Island.
Do you know anything about that?
Did she just say Sky Island?
She's crazy.
Like I was saying, if you know
how to get to Sky Island...
This is who I think is it!
Sky Island, what an idiot!
What the...
You can look at the long pose yourself!
It's pointed at the sky, plain as day!
Hey, check it out!
Do I look like the log foes now?
No one trusts those things anymore.
They break if you breathe wrong.
You got me there, kid.
I can't believe you guys
are putting open to such
a ridiculous legend like
an island in the sky.
Especially considering
how little you know.
Like at the thousands of weird currents
cutting through the Grand Line,
one of the weirdest is
called the knock-up stream.
looks to me like this is
the first you've ever heard
about it any ship that
gets caught in a knock-up
stream is catapulted into
the sky and later slams back
into the ocean years ago a
bunch of ignorant sailors saw
ships falling from the sky
and assumed there must be
an island up there somewhere
in their minds how else
could a ship get up that
high ridiculous anything that
seems supernatural always
has a rational explanation.
Anything a man can
dream will eventually be
explained and let me tell
you the truth will hurt.
What a shame.
Look, I was gonna let you join my
crew if you'd pass the test of the new
era, but it seems like you're a lost cause.
Thing is, the time of
pirates' dreams are over.
The City of Gold, the Emerald
Ruins, and the Great One Piece.
The fools who dream of
these fictional treasures
don't notice the real
treasures that surround them.
In this age of oceans,
the very men who are brave enough
and capable of navigating currents
end up chasing these ridiculous
dreams and die in the process.
Whenever people speak
of these dead idiots,
they always say he was happy
because he died living his dreams.
Ha!
No, he died because he was a fool.
So when I see people chasing dreams
of One Piece, I get disgusted!
Louie!
You're a weak pirate, just like they were.
And as long as you're hacking
around, you'll make us,
the real pirates, look like trash!
Get out of here, you scrawny punk.
You're killing our bugs.
Way to go, Bellamy.
Bellamy, give these people what they want!
Tear into them.
I'd be more than happy to entertain.
Luffy, Zoro, forget all that pacifist
crap I was talking about earlier.
And take this jerk out.
Zoro.
No matter what happens, don't fight back.